A Guide to the Blackley Family Papers, 1830-2016: SC 0232
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Series 1: Correspondence, 1830-2011
  - Chuck Blackley, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Chuck Blackley, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Catherine Matthews Blackley, undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Chas Blackley, undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Chuck Blackley, undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Series 2: Personal Papers, 1857-2016
  Series 2: Personal Papers, 1857-2015, is comprised of personal papers, diaries, and other documents that highlight the careers and interests of the family members. R.H. Bassett's papers include Confederate government and military documents pertaining to promotions, recruitment, and resignation.
  Another unique piece of this collection from the early period is the Belle Bassett Diary, 1873-1879, which offers a glimpse of the post-war years for a child growing up in the South.
  Chas Blackley, in addition to his letters from the trip to Europe, also kept a diary of his experiences. This diary covers the personal and public incidents of his travels.
  More information about individual members of family is available here in the form of detailed histories of specific family lines (Blackley, Bassett, Hoge, etc.), through family trees, and biographical information.
  Other items of note from Chas Blackley are the many manuscripts of novels and plays that he wrote in the early-to-mid 1930s.
  - Sallie Scott Poetry, 1855-1858, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Sarah Scott, 1857, 1929, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - C. C. Phillips, 1859 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - R. H. Bassett, 1861-1870 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Marriage Licenses, 1862, 1884, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Family Papers, 1865-2009, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Obituaries, 1868-2010, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Sallie S. Bassett, 1870-1916 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Belle Bassett Diary, 1873-1879 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Belle Bassett Autograph Books, 1881-1882 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Belle B. Blackley, 1882, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Wesleyan Female Institute, 1882-1886 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Corn Festival Pamphlet, ca. 1890 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Military Discharge, 1898 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - E.J. Cushing, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Geo. W. Blackley, 1911 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Birth Certificates, 1913, 1931, 1951, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Catherine Matthews Blackley, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - James H. Blackley, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Wills, 1919, 1927, 1949, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Chas Blackley, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Mary Blackley, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Chas Blackley, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Chas Blackley, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - James H. Blackley, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Catherine Matthews School Related Materials, 1927-1944, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Chas Blackley, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - James H. Blackley, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Chas Blackley Diary, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Chas Blackley, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Chas Blackley Diary, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Smoke Screen, Fort Eustis, Virginia, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Chas Blackley, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Chas Blackley Journal, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Chas Blackley, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - The Commonwealth Club, 1931-1938 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Estate of George W. Blackley, 1931-1937 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Chas Blackley, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Chas Blackley Diary, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Edited "Between Two Fires" Script, Chas Blackley, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Edited "Echo" Manuscript, Chas Blackley, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Mrs. E.J. Cushing, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Samuel Travers Phillips, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Chas Blackley, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Chas Blackley Diary, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Edited "Full Cargo" Manuscript, Chas Blackley, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Edited "Yellow Cargo" Manuscript, Chas Blackley, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - "Full Cargo" Manuscript Draft, Chas Blackley, ca. 1933 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - "The High Road" Manuscript Draft, Chas Blackley, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - "Yellow Cargo" Manuscript Draft, Chas Blackley, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Chas Blackley, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Chas Blackley Diary, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Edited Incomplete Manuscript, Chas Blackley, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Novel Outlines, Chas Blackley, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Passports, 1934, 1968-1969, 1975, 2000, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - The Staunton Players, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Catherine Matthews, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Chas Blackley, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Mary Blackley, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - WSVA Shares, Chas Blackley, 1935-1938 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Catherine Matthews Blackley, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Chas Blackley, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Chas Blackley, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Catherine Matthews, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Chas Blackley, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Household Inventory, Chas Blackley, 1938-1944 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Ration Books, 1940-1946 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Catherine Blackley, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Chas Blackley, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Catherine Blackley, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Chas Blackley, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Catherine Blackley, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Chas Blackley, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Catherine Blackley, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Chas Blackley, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Chas Blackley, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Chas Blackley, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Catherine Blackley, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Chas Blackley, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Chas Blackley, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Chas Blackley, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Chas Blackley, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Chas Blackley, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Chas Blackley, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - May Day Pamphlets from Stuart Hall, Susan Blackley, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Transcription of Signalman Charles Coatesworth Phillips' 1864 diary and message book, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Chas Blackley, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Catherine Blackley, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Chas Blackley, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Glamour Manor - Beverly Hills, 1956, 1957-1961 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Belle Blackley Trust (Folder 1 of 3), 1958-1968 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Belle Blackley Trust (Folder 2 of 3), 1958-1968 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Belle Blackley Trust (Folder 3 of 3), 1958-1968 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Chas Blackley, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Associated Press Bulletin concerning JFK Assassination, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Shenandoah Discount Inc. Bankruptcy, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Susan Blackley, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Chas Blackley, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Pat Blackley, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Death Certificates, 1974, 1999, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - A Salute to Senator Harry T. Byrd Jr., 1975 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Chas Blackley, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - "I Remember It Well" Drafts, Catherine Matthews Blackley, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Pat Blackley, ca.1984 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Pat Blackley, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Pat Blackley, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Chas Blackley, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Chas Blackley, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Examples of projects undertaken under Charles P. Blackley Jr. PE, ca. 1990s (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Chas Blackley, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Chuck Blackley, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Chuck Blackley, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Catherine Blackley, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Chuck Blackley, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Chuck Blackley, 2015 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Blackley Family Bios, 2016, undated (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - "Between Two Fires" Script, Chas Blackley, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Catherine Blackley, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Chas Blackley, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Chuck Blackley, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Drafts of Multiple Incomplete Manuscripts, Chas Blackley, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Duplicate of Blackley Family Bible, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - John McNair and Associates, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Radio Broadcasting Scripts, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Notes of story of blind boy, Chas Blackley, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - "The story about the war" by Catherine Blackley, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Series 3: Ephemera, 1856-2004
  Series 3: Ephemera, 1856-2004, houses many unique items such as hundreds of stamps (U.S., Confederate, and international), brochures, certificates, awards, diplomas, and pamphlets from events such as the 1932 Los Angeles Olympics and the 1933 World's Fair in Chicago, and dance cards. The aforementioned diplomas and certificates document the Blackley family's achievements and graduations from various schools and universities, including the University of Virginia, the State Teacher's College at Harrisonburg, and Virginia Tech. Many of the manuals and booklets used in Chas' various military training can be found in this series.
  There are also newspaper clippings that share stories directly related to family members or address significant events of the time. These include awards won by the family, news about new jobs or graduations, historic events like D-Day, and John F. Kennedy's assassination.
  One of the more locally relevant pieces is a pamphlet entitled "Dedication of the Shenandoah National Park" (1936). It lists the planned dedication speech from President Franklin D. Roosevelt given at Big Meadows as the key event.
  This series also includes one oversize box of 3D ephemeral objects. Objects of interest include a Kodak No. 2 Folding Autographic Brownie camera (1917-1926) owned by Chas Blackley and inscribed with the names of Blackley and the SS Gertrude Kellogg, Dr. Charles Coatesworth Phillips' small leather medicine case with glass bottles that he took on house calls, several pairs of glasses, a glass plate photograph of Susie E. Phillips, and assorted World's Fair ephemera.
  Stored separately are multiple flags that are likely from Chas' 1930 voyage in the Pacific. There is a large and small Japanese flag, a small Chinese [pre-communist revolution] flag, and a small Philippine national flag. An additional flag dates to WWI and features the United States flag surrounded by smaller flags of all our allies from that conflict.
  - Blackley Family Newspaper Clippings, 1856-2012, bulk 1932-1938 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Dance Cards, 1860, 1882, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Confederate States of America stamps, 1861-1865 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Phillips Family diploma, VMI class poster, New Market cadet poster, 1861-1907, undated (Box 1:3, Folder 1)
  - Phillips Family certificates and diplomas (folder 1 of 2), 1866-1867 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Phillips Family certificates and diplomas (folder 2 of 2), 1866-1867 (Box OV1, Folder 1)
  - Currency, Bonds, and Certificates, 1861-1948, bulk 1861-1865 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Set of Flower Picture Cards, 1870 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - George Washington Stamps, ca. 1880-1900 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Assorted keychains and trinkets, 1881, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Benjamin Franklin Stamps, 1881-1889 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - United States Stamped Envelopes, 1801-1901 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Assorted 3D objects, 1884-1982, undated (Box OV2)
  - Assorted Booklets (folder 1 of 2), 1886-1984 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Assorted Booklets (folder 2 of 2), 1886-1984 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Parker County, Texas Immigrants Guide, ca.1889 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Ulysses S. Grant Stamps, ca. 1890 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - International Stamps, 1894-1974 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Labor Day Ribbon, 1897 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - United States Commemorative Stamps, ca.1900 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Life Magazines, 1902-1903 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1907-1998 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Assorted medals and awards, 1910, 1954, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - The first capital of Texas, Newspaper Clippings, ca. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Surety Coupon Collection Book, Mrs. E.J. Cushing, 1915 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Assorted flags, ca. 1918, 1930, undated (Box 1:3, Folder 2)
  - Army and Training Regulations, 1922-1930 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Cigar Band Collection, Chas Blackley, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Assorted Maps, 1925-1982 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Catherine Matthews Blackley certificate and diplomas, 1927-1935 (Box OV1, Folder 2)
  - Chas Blackley certificates and diploma, 1927-1947 (Box OV1, Folder 3)
  - Military Manuals, Chas Blackley, 1928, 1941-1943 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Box of matches from Darlen, Manchuria or Keelung, Formosa, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Charles Blackley military hats, 1930, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Custom Christmas Cards, Chas Blackley, 1931, 1937, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Assorted Event Tickets, 1931-1935 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Airline Luggage Tags, 1932, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Assorted Brochures (Folder 1 of 2), 1932-1992 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Assorted Brochures (Folder 2 of 2), 1932-1992 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Assorted U.S. Destination Pamphlets and Cards, ca. 1932 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Christmas Card Puzzle, Chas Blackley, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Los Angeles Olympics Booklets and Brochures, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - The Press Club Heckler, 1932 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Bert Cooklsey Poetry, Newspaper Clippings, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - World's Fair, Chicago, Brochures and Pamphlets (folder 1 of 2), 1933 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - World's Fair, Chicago, Brochures and Pamphlets (folder 2 of 2), 1933 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - European Ephemera, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Pastel caricature, likely Chas Blackley, 1934 (Box OV1, Folder 4)
  - Dedication of the Shenandoah National Park Pamphlet, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - WSVA Newspaper Clippings, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous pins, 1934, 1982-1984, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - "Merry Christmas" charcoal drawing, Chas Blackley and Santa Claus, 1937 (Box OV1, Folder 5)
  - Military patches, ca. 1940s (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Assorted military pins, 1943, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Chas Blackley Certificates, 1944, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Major of St. Lo, Newspaper Clippings, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Pass for Camp Crowder, MO, Catherine Blackley, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Pocket Service Prayer Book and Military Missal, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Stamp Collection, 1944-1988 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Alcoholic Beverage Control Board Sales Permit No. 2, Civilian Registrants, 1944, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Army Service Forces: Annual Report, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - War Department Signal Center Printouts, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Campaign buttons, 1950, 1976, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Life Magazine, April 16, 1951 (Box OV1, Folder 6)
  - Pencil drawing, Blackley Family residence at 317 E. Beverley St. Staunton, 1959 (Box OV1, Folder 7)
  - Civil War related color posters, 1963, undated (Box OV1, Folder 8)
  - Chuck Blackley Certificates (folder 1 of 2), 1963-1998 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Chuck Blackley Certificates (folder 2 of 2), 1963-1998 (Box OV1, Folder 9)
  - Assorted Engineering Calculators used prior to Computers, ca. 1965 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Rotary International, Mexico City, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Assorted Tokens and Coins, 1969, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Program, Robert E. Lee High School Graduation Exercises, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Patricia D. Fry, Robert E. Lee High School Diploma, 1970 (Box OV1, Folder 16)
  - Pocket Circular Slide Rule, Chuck Blackley, ca.1970 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Reprint of "Shenandoah, I Long to Hear You" article from April 1970 National Geographic Magazine, ca.1970 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Patricia Fry Blackley Diplomas, Elizabeth Brant School of Business, Blue Ridge Community College, 1971, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Chuck Blackley Diploma, Virginia Tech, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Marble Valley Pumped Storage Project, ca. 1975 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Assorted Membership and Identification Cards, 1976-1997 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Patricia Blackley Certificates, 1986, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - International Star Registry certificates and maps, 1990 (Box OV1, Folder 10)
  - Star Registry Documents and Maps, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Rotary Foundation Award, Chas Blackley, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Contents of Chas Blackley's Wallet, ca. 1999 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - White House Press Pass for Submarine Texas Christening, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Assorted Business Cards, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Assorted Postcards, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Assorted United States Stamps, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Booklet of "The Eight Grand National Pictures in the Rotunda of the U.S. Capitol at Washington", undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Booklet of Washingtion Architecture, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Catherine Matthews Blackley sketch of monogrammed dinnerware, undated (Box OV1, Folder 11)
  - Charles Blackley Custom Bookplates and Stamp, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Chesterfield Cigarettes Tin, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Coasters, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Cunard Line Labels and Tags, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Dallas Opera House "The Humming Bird" Play Advertisement, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Mary Blackley Silhouette, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Military pins and dog tags, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Ephemera, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Rapid City, South Dakota Advertisements, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Sketches of people by [Catherine?] Matthews, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Small Fan, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - "Story of Appomattox" Newspaper Clipping, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Toy Town Post Office, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - United States Numerical Stamps, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Valentine Writer Booklets, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - West Virginia "Coal Country" 3D Cast, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - WTON Sugar Bowl Advertisement, undated (Box OV1, Folder 12)
- Series 4: Photographs, ca.1861-1989
  Series 4, Photographs, ca. 1861-1989, includes a large number of pictures from both of Chas Blackley's trips to Asia and the Pacific in 1930 and his journey through Europe in 1934.
  There are also a number of rare pictures of the Civilian Military Training Camp (CMTC) experience at Ft. Eustis, Virginia, from 1928, and to our knowledge might be the only ones publicly available.
  As Catherine Matthews Blackley was a graduate of the State Teacher's College at Harrisonburg (now JMU), there many pictures from her time on campus during the early 1930s in this collection.
  Another rare item housed here is an ambrotype of an unidentified woman which is located in Miscellaneous, 1884-1993 (folder 3 of 4). The subject's identity is unknown, but the style of production dates the piece to around 1858. Given that date and the apparent age of the woman, it is plausible that the subject is Sarah Lane Scott, Sallie Scott Bassett's mother.
  - R.H. Bassett, ca. 1861-1870 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Great Grandfather and Grandmother Gilkeson, ca. 1862 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Photo Album owned by Rev. Richard H. Phillips while in Civil War prison in Ohio, 1865 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Belle Bassett Blackley, 1883, 1891, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous (folder 1 of 4), 1884-1993 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous (folder 2 of 4), 1884-1993 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous (folder 3 of 4), 1884-1993 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous (folder 4 of 4), 1884-1993 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Assorted George W. Blackley, 1886, ca.1890, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Assorted C.T. Phillips, ca.1908, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Assorted Chas Blackley, 1910-1993, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Pictures sent to Mrs. M.E. Phillips, ca. 1914 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Chas Hoge portrait, 1919 (Box OV1, Folder 13)
  - Catherine Matthews Family, 1927, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Civilian Military Training Camp, Ft. Eustis, VA, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Chas Blackley, Regimental Color Bearer, Church in the grove (1928); Staunton-Augusta County Agricultural Fair (September 1956), 1928, September 1956 (Box OV1, Folder 14)
  - Catherine Matthews, ca. 1930s (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Commonwealth Club, Staunton, VA, ca. 1930s (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Dixie Theater Fire, Staunton, VA, ca. 1930s (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Manila and Manchuria, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Negatives of SS Gertrude Kellogg, Panama Canal, China, Japan, Phillipine Islands, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Car Crash, 1931 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Catherine Matthews Blackley class photographs, 1931, 1938, undated (Box OV1, Folder 15)
  - Catalinia Island, ca.1932 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Chas Blackley, Olympic Stadium, Los Angeles, Calif., 1932 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Cheyenne, Wyo., ca. 1932 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Cleveland, O., ca. 1932 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Denver, Col., 1932 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Detroit, Mi., ca. 1932 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles, 1932 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Niagra Falls, ca. 1932 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Omaha, Neb., ca. 1932 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Postcards with pictures of Woodrow Wilson and Staunton, VA, ca. 1932 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Salt Lake City, 1932 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - San Francisco, Calif., ca. 1932 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Yellowstone, ca. 1932 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Yosemite, ca. 1932 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Bert, 1933 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Chicago, Ill., ca. 1933 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Assorted European Cities, ca. 1934 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Assorted European Cities Negatives, ca. 1934 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Berlin and Brussels, 1934 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Catherine Matthews, 1934-1938 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Florence, Venice, Vienna, Munich, Oberammagon, Nuremberg, 1934 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - London, Liverpool, Oxford, R.M.S. Laconia, ca. 1934 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Lucerne and Paris, ca. 1934 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Passport Photgraphs, Chas Blackley, 1934 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - R.M.S. Laconia, ca. 1934 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Rome, Fontainebleau, Lucerne, ca. 1934 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Rome, Paris, Battlefields, 1934 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Staunton Airport, 1934 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Assorted Catherine Matthews Blackley, 1935-1968, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - WSVA Antenna Tower, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Assorted Chas and Catherine Blackley, 1937, 1982, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Chas Blackley Car Crash, 1937 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - A. David Khan, 1938, 1989, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Chas and Catherine Blackley Wedding, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Assorted Mary Blackley Taylor, 1939, 1964, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Blackley Family Homes, 1944, 1958, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Camp Crowder, MO and Washington, D.C. during WWII, 1944, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Assorted Fannie Blackley Cushing, 1947-1952, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Assorted Susan Blackley, 1947-1992, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Assorted Blackley Family Group Photos, 1948-1993, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Assorted Chuck Blackley, 1951-1984, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)